bargain.com 2013-03-15

# Bargain.com - Find Your Local Daily Bargains

Thank you for visiting Bargain.com (the “Site”). The Site is an Internet property of Neverblue Media Company and its affiliated companies (“Neverblue”, “we” or “us”). This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) outlines the privacy practices associated with the Site. You agree to this Privacy Policy, in its entirety, when you: (a) access or use the Site; (b) agree to receive e-mail from us via the Site, or any other means; and/or (c) create an account on the Site. At Neverblue we are committed to maintaining both a high standard of privacy and a high standard of data protection in all of our activities. Our Privacy Policy was created to ensure we preserve the confidentiality, accuracy and security of your personal information. This Privacy Policy guides us in the collection, use, retention and disclosure of your personal information. If you would like to discuss any concerns in person, please feel free to contact us at any time.

## Scope

This Privacy Policy applies to information about Bargain.com customers that is collected, used or disclosed by Neverblue. It also applies to the management of information in any form whether oral, electronic or written. We consider “personal information” to be information about an identifiable individual.

## Third Party Links

Bargain.com contains links to other websites owned and operated by our Third Party Providers. Where you request information from Third Party Providers, Neverblue may transfer you directly to the websites of such Third Party Providers. In some cases, you may be required to provide certain information to register or complete a transaction at such website. However, you need to be aware that these sites may have different security or privacy policies from us. We cannot be responsible for any information you give to them or for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. We do not endorse, nor are we responsible for the accuracy of, the privacy policies and/or terms and conditions of such websites. All Third Party Providers are independent third parties and are not affiliated with us.

## Personally Identifiable Information

We collect your Personally Identifiable Information (PII) when you sign up for an account with us and in order to allow you to purchase or register for certain products, services and applications and complete those transactions; to enter contests; to subscribe to email newsletters; and to provide you with services or information that may be of interest to you. The types of PII that we collect at the Site may include, without limitation, your: (a) name; (b) e-mail address; c) date of birth; d) gender; and (e) any and all other information requested on the applicable registration form.

## Sharing your Information

Our use of your PII. We'll only use your PII for sending you information about your account with us, or about offers that are available on your account or other services available from Bargain or our partners. 

Sharing your PII with third parties. By submitting your PII on the Site, you agree that we may share and forward such information with Third Party Providers in order to complete your request for specific products and/or services that you applied for at the Site from such Third Party Providers, and that they may use such information for any lawful purposes, subject to any restrictions contained herein or in the terms and conditions or privacy policies of such Third Party Providers. Any information that you supply through the Site to any Third Party Providers shall be governed by the applicable Third Party Providers‘ privacy policy. The PII collected about you when you visit this site may also, where applicable, be disclosed to any member of our group. This includes, where applicable, our affiliates, our subsidiaries, our holding company and/or other companies within our group or any competent legal, regulatory or law enforcement authority. In the case of a regulatory or legal authority, you will not be told of this disclosure or the reasons why and you'll be waiving any and all rights that you may have in connection with such disclosure. Finally if you breach our Terms and Conditions, we may share your personal details with our professional advisers or other appropriate third parties.

Neverblue is a Canadian company therefore our collection, use and disclosure of personal information is governed by the Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act, (S.C. 2000, c.5) (the “Act”). The Act gives you the right to access the information that we hold about you. Please note that any demand for access must be made in accordance with the Act and may be subject to a small fee which covers our costs in providing you with the information requested. Should you wish to receive details that we hold about you please contact us at the contact information provided below.

## Non-Personally Identifiable Information

We may collect certain non-personally identifiable information about you when you visit many of the pages of the Site through the use of Cookies, as explained below. This non-personally identifiable information includes, without limitation, the type of browser that you use (e.g., Internet Explorer or Mozilla Firefox), your IP address, the type of operating system that you use (e.g., Windows or Mac OS) and the domain name of your Internet service provider, and any referring websites. We use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of the Site, to enable us to personalize your Internet experience, and contacting you when we need to give you some information about your account or when we have an offer that you can use with your account. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze Site usage, as well as to offer you products and services. We also reserve the right to use aggregate or group data about our visitors for any and all lawful purposes. Aggregate or group data is data that describes the demographics, usage and/or characteristics of our visitors as a group. By visiting and/or supplying your information at the Site, you agree to allow us to provide such aggregate data to third parties.

## Cookies 

When you visit the Site, we send a cookie and/or gif file (“Cookie”) to assign an anonymous, unique identifier to your Internet browser. A Cookie is a piece of data stored on your hard drive containing non-personally identifiable information about you. Cookies have many benefits to enhance your experience at the Site. Neverblue reserves the right to retain Cookie data indefinitely. We use a third-party tracking service that uses Cookies and web beacons to track non-personally identifiable information about visitors and site visitation to our site in the aggregate. To disable and reject certain Cookies, follow the instructions associated with your Internet browser. Most browsers will allow you to erase Cookies from your computer hard drive, block acceptance of Cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. However, if you block or erase Cookies, we may not be able to restore any preferences or customize settings you previously specified, and our ability to personalize your online experience would be limited. Please refer to your browser instructions or “help” screen to learn more about these functions. You can also visit www.aboutcookies.org for more information about Cookies.

Please note that if one of our advertisers, or one of the sites that referred you to us, uses Cookies then we're unable to access or control this. As well as Cookies we use a number of technologies for helping us understand how you like to use our sites. The information they collect is very limited - just a number, time, date and details of the page visited and a few other details like the type of web browser that you use or your IP address. We can't use this information to identify you, but it helps us improve our service. Some of our web pages may also contain electronic images for something called 'pixel tracking' - this lets us count how many people have visited us. We may also carry pixel trackers placed by third party advertisers, but they don't have any information that could identify you. Our advertisers may also use Cookies, over which we have no control. Such Cookies (if used) would be downloaded once you click on advertisements on our website.

This website also uses Google Analytics; a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. Google Analytics uses Cookies to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google's behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. By using this Site, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above.

## Opt-Out/Unsubscribe

When you submit personally identifiable information through the Site, you have opted-in to receive information and marketing communications from the Third Party Provider. When contacted by any of these companies or third parties, you should notify them directly of your choices regarding the use of your information. To opt-out of having future third party marketing communications sent to you, you will be required to unsubscribe with the applicable third parties.

## Minors

We do not knowingly collect information from minors under eighteen (18) years of age. No information should be submitted through the Site by individuals under eighteen (18) years of age. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate and monitor the interactive activities of their children.

## Changes to Privacy Policy

We reserve the right, in our sole discretion, to change, modify, add and/or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time and without prior notice to you. Since we do not collect and store any of your information, we are unable tpo contact you directly regarding any changes to this Privacy Policy. Notice regarding any Privacy Policy changes will be placed in a prominent location on the Site and will take effect immediately upon their posting on the Site. Please check the Site periodically for any changes. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of any and all changes.

## Contact Us

For more information please contact our Chief Privacy Officer as follows:  
E-mail: privacy@neverblue.com  
Attention: Chief Privacy Officer  

## Effective September 19, 2012
